<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Docs on Adrestia User-Guide</title><link>https://input-output-hk.github.io/adrestia/docs/</link><description>Recent content in Docs on Adrestia User-Guide</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://input-output-hk.github.io/adrestia/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Architecture</title><link>https://input-output-hk.github.io/adrestia/docs/architecture/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://input-output-hk.github.io/adrestia/docs/architecture/</guid><description>High-Level Diagram mermaid.initialize({ flowchart: { useMaxWidth:true } }); erDiagram CARDANO-NODE ||--o{ CARDANO-WALLET : sends-blocks-and-receives-txs CARDANO-NODE ||--o{ CARDANO-DB-SYNC : sends-blocks CARDANO-NODE ||--o{ CARDANO-SUBMIT-API : receives-txs CARDANO-DB-SYNC ||--|| POSTGRESQL : dumps-into POSTGRESQL ||--|| CARDANO-GRAPHQL : is-queried POSTGRESQL ||--|| CARDANO-EXPLORER-API : is-queried Components cardano-node The core cardano-node, which will support Ouroboros Praos.
Supported environments: Linux (64-bits), MacOS (64-bits), Windows (64-bits), Docker cardano-db-sync A necessary middleware to power both cardano-rest and cardano-graphql.</description></item><item><title>Installation Instructions</title><link>https://input-output-hk.github.io/adrestia/docs/installation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://input-output-hk.github.io/adrestia/docs/installation/</guid><description>Using Docker (recommended) Docker images are continuously built and deployed on dockerhub under specific tags. Using docker provides the fastest and easiest user experience for setting up the Cardano stack. You should prefer this solution over building from sources unless you have really good reasons not to. The following images are available for each component of the Adrestia architecture:
Repository Tags Documentation inputoutput/cardano-node master, MAJ.</description></item><item><title>Migrating From SL</title><link>https://input-output-hk.github.io/adrestia/docs/migrating-from-sl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://input-output-hk.github.io/adrestia/docs/migrating-from-sl/</guid><description>I am using explorer from cardano-sl, what should I do? The API from the old explorer has been ported identically to cardano-submit-api. This component is part of cardano-rest. Source code that is dealing with the explorer API from cardano-sl should be straightforward to migrate. See the installation instructions and documentation available on cardano-rest for more details.
The setup is here a bit different. With cardano-sl, the explorer is mounted directly on the core node as one monolith and can be turned on and off.</description></item><item><title>API References</title><link>https://input-output-hk.github.io/adrestia/docs/api-references/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://input-output-hk.github.io/adrestia/docs/api-references/</guid><description>Components Component Link cardano-wallet https://input-output-hk.github.io/cardano-wallet/api/edge cardano-submit-api https://input-output-hk.github.io/cardano-rest/submit-api/ cardano-explorer-api https://input-output-hk.github.io/cardano-rest/explorer-api/ cardano-graphql Soon available. About cardano-wallet
Cardano-wallet comes with a command-line interface that can be used as a quick alternative to cURL or wget to interact with a server running on localhost. Every endpoint of the API is mapped to a corresponding command which often offers a better user experience than directly interacting with the API as a human (API are for programs, command-lines are for humans).</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://input-output-hk.github.io/adrestia/docs/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://input-output-hk.github.io/adrestia/docs/faq/</guid><description>Why aren&amp;#39;t my unused addresses imported when I restore a wallet? ... This is by vertue of the blockchain. An unused address is by definition unused. Meaning that is doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist on the chain and only exists locally, in the context of the software that has generated it. Different softwares may use different rules to generate addresses. For example in the past, cardano-sl wallets used a method called random derivation where addresses will be created from a root seed and a random index that is stored with the address itself.</description></item></channel></rss>